mylunchmoney.com 2015-09-13

# MyLunchMoney

### _Last updated: 04/16/2013_

Heartland Payment Systems, Inc. (“Heartland,” “we,” “us,” “our”) recognizes the importance of maintaining effective privacy practices. This Privacy Policy explains the online data collection and use policies that apply to the websites, mobile applications and online services that are owned or controlled by Heartland and are linked to this Policy page. 

We reserve the right to transfer any information we collect in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including any shares in the company) or any portion or combination of our products, services, businesses and/or assets. Should such a transaction occur (whether a divestiture, merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, liquidation, or similar transaction or proceeding), we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that any transferred information is treated in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

By using our websites, mobile applications, or online services you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to agree to this Privacy Policy, do not use our websites, mobile applications, or online services. 

### Information Collection and Use

If you request information from us through our online contact forms, we ask for and store the business-related information you provide (such as name, address, email address, telephone number, etc.) to assist us in responding to your request. When you visit our websites or mobile applications (or when you use any of our online services) we may collect or have collected certain information about your computer or device through technology such as cookies, web beacons, or other tracking/recording tools. The information collected may include, but is not limited to, IP addresses, referring URLs, access times, browser types, device types, mobile device identifiers, geolocation or information about your interactions with our websites, mobile applications or services. (Note that a “cookie” is a text file placed on a computer’s hard drive or stored on a mobile device; a “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server.) 

We may use the information described in this paragraph to, among other things, (i) operate our services, including by remembering information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you sign in to your account, (ii) identify and protect our customers, (iii) control unauthorized use or abuse of our services, (iv) provide custom, personalized content and information, which could include advertising, (v) monitor aggregate traffic patterns on our websites, mobile applications, and services, and (vi) analyze and improve our services. 

### Sharing of Information

Your personal information may be shared with our employees, contractors, consultants, affiliates and other parties who require such information to assist us with providing our services to you and in establishing, maintaining and managing our relationship with you. 

We may also share information with our service providers and business partners to help us monitor usage and other analytics regarding our services, and to help us improve these offerings. When we share your information with our service providers and business partners, we only provide the information that these third parties reasonably need to perform their functions. 

We may share or disclose your information if we determine, in our sole discretion, that we are required to do so under applicable law or regulatory requirements, or if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to prevent harm or financial loss, or in connection with preventing fraud or illegal activity, and/or to enforce our Terms of Use. 

### Children’s Privacy

Heartland’s websites, mobile applications and services are intended for use strictly by adults. Heartland does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If Heartland obtains knowledge that it has collected personal information from a child under 13 in retrievable form in its files, Heartland will delete that information. 

### Data Protection and Storage

Heartland maintains reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect the confidentiality of information transmitted online, including but not limited to encryption, firewalls and SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). Heartland has implemented policies and practices pursuant to various security rules and regulations relating to the security and safeguarding of payment cardholder data, including the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS). However, no precautions, means, or method of transmission which uses the internet or method of storage is absolutely 100% secure. For these reasons, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your personal information. 

Heartland is not liable for loss of passwords due to user negligence. If you believe your password has been lost or compromised, we recommend that you immediately change your password. 

We may store and process information in the United States or any other country in which Heartland or its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. Heartland may transfer information that we collect about you, including personal information, to parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, or service providers across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which Heartland or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

### Third-Party Websites and Services

Our websites, mobile applications, or services may provide links to third-party websites or services – none of which are governed by this Privacy Policy. To the extent that any linked third-party websites or services you visit are not owned or controlled by Heartland, we are not responsible for those websites’ or services’ content or information practices. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policies of any site or service before providing any personal information. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion. We will post changes on this page and indicate the “last modified” date at the top of this page. Please check back often for any updates. Your continued use of our website, mobile application or services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
